[
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_GatherAllies",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 58,
		"Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_GatherAllies_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99F_Sun_03",
		"AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_01",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_10 || 99_MSQ_56",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_GatherAllies_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT4",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99F_MSQ01_GatherAllies_title",
		"Description": "@99F_MSQ01_GatherAllies_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99F_MSQ01_GatherAllies_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99F_MSQ01_GatherAllies_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99F_MSQ01_GatherAllies_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99F_MSQ01_GatherAllies_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_MeetWiseman",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 58,
		"Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_MeetWiseman_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99F_Grace_04",
		"AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_02",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_01",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_MeetWiseman_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Legwear_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99F_MSQ02_MeetWiseman_title",
		"Description": "@99F_MSQ02_MeetWiseman_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99F_MSQ02_MeetWiseman_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99F_MSQ02_MeetWiseman_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99F_MSQ02_MeetWiseman_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99F_MSQ02_MeetWiseman_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_CreateRefuge",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 58,
		"Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_CreateRefuge_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99F_Sun_04",
		"AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_03",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_02",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_CreateRefuge_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99F_MSQ03_CreateRefuge_title",
		"Description": "@99F_MSQ03_CreateRefuge_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99F_MSQ03_CreateRefuge_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99F_MSQ03_CreateRefuge_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99F_MSQ03_CreateRefuge_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99F_MSQ03_CreateRefuge_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_InspireAllies",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 58,
		"Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_InspireAllies_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99F_Sun_04a",
		"AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_04",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_03",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_InspireAllies_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "HoningStoneT4",
		"ItemRewardQty": 3,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99F_MSQ04_InspireAllies_title",
		"Description": "@99F_MSQ04_InspireAllies_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99F_MSQ04_InspireAllies_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99F_MSQ04_InspireAllies_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99F_MSQ04_InspireAllies_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99F_MSQ04_InspireAllies_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_MeetEmpress",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 59,
		"Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_MeetEmpress_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99F_Empress_01",
		"AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_05",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_04",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_MeetEmpress_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Footwear_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99F_MSQ05_MeetEmpress_title",
		"Description": "@99F_MSQ05_MeetEmpress_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99F_MSQ05_MeetEmpress_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99F_MSQ05_MeetEmpress_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99F_MSQ05_MeetEmpress_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99F_MSQ05_MeetEmpress_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_AscendPeak",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 59,
		"Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_AscendPeak_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99F_Empress_01a",
		"AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_06",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_05",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_AscendPeak_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Chestwear_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99F_MSQ06_AscendPeak_title",
		"Description": "@99F_MSQ06_AscendPeak_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99F_MSQ06_AscendPeak_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99F_MSQ06_AscendPeak_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99F_MSQ06_AscendPeak_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99F_MSQ06_AscendPeak_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_CreateIncense",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 59,
		"Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_CreateIncense_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99F_Sun_05a",
		"AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_07",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_06",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_CreateIncense_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT4",
		"ItemRewardQty": 10,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99F_MSQ07_CreateIncense_title",
		"Description": "@99F_MSQ07_CreateIncense_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99F_MSQ07_CreateIncense_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99F_MSQ07_CreateIncense_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99F_MSQ07_CreateIncense_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99F_MSQ07_CreateIncense_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 59,
		"Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99F_Liang_01",
		"AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_08",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_07 && !Archetype_Mercenary && !Archetype_Warmonger && !Archetype_Tracker && !Archetype_Musketeer && !Archetype_Occultist && !Archetype_Theurgist && !Archetype_Wanderer",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_title",
		"Description": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"NOTE": "Soul Trial"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_destroyer",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 59,
		"Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99F_Liang_01",
		"AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_08",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_07 && Archetype_Warmonger",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_success_destroyer",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Handwear_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_title",
		"Description": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"NOTE": "Soul Trial alt"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_musketeer",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 59,
		"Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99F_Liang_01",
		"AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_08",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_07 && Archetype_Musketeer",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_success_musketeer",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Handwear_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_title",
		"Description": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"NOTE": "Soul Trial alt"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_mystic",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 59,
		"Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99F_Liang_01",
		"AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_08",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_07 && Archetype_Theurgist",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_success_mystic",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Handwear_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_title",
		"Description": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"NOTE": "Soul Trial alt"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_occultist",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 59,
		"Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99F_Liang_01",
		"AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_08",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_07 && Archetype_Occultist",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_success_occultist",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Handwear_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_title",
		"Description": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"NOTE": "Soul Trial alt"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_ranger",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 59,
		"Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99F_Liang_01",
		"AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_08",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_07 && Archetype_Tracker",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_success_ranger",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Handwear_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_title",
		"Description": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"NOTE": "Soul Trial alt"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_soldier",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 59,
		"Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99F_Liang_01",
		"AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_08",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_07 && Archetype_Mercenary",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_success_soldier",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Handwear_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_title",
		"Description": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"NOTE": "Soul Trial alt"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_swordsman",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 59,
		"Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99F_Liang_01",
		"AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_08",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_07 && Archetype_Wanderer",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_success_swordsman",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Handwear_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_title",
		"Description": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"NOTE": "Soul Trial alt"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_ReuniteFamily",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_ReuniteFamily_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99F_Grace_08a",
		"AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_08",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_ReuniteFamily_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Headgear_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99F_MSQ09_ReuniteFamily_title",
		"Description": "@99F_MSQ09_ReuniteFamily_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99F_MSQ09_ReuniteFamily_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99F_MSQ09_ReuniteFamily_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99F_MSQ09_ReuniteFamily_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99F_MSQ09_ReuniteFamily_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_StealBoat",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_StealBoat_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99F_Grace_09",
		"AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_10",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_09",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_StealBoat_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 10,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99F_MSQ10_StealBoat_title",
		"Description": "@99F_MSQ10_StealBoat_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99F_MSQ10_StealBoat_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99F_MSQ10_StealBoat_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99F_MSQ10_StealBoat_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99F_MSQ10_StealBoat_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightEmpress",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightEmpress_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99F_Sun_08",
		"AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_11",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_10",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_FightEmpress_success",
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99F_MSQ11_FightEmpress_title",
		"Description": "@99F_MSQ11_FightEmpress_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99F_MSQ11_FightEmpress_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99F_MSQ11_FightEmpress_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99F_MSQ11_FightEmpress_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99F_MSQ11_FightEmpress_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"NOTE": "Soul Trial"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99F_MSQ_ER_DeliverPoem",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99F_MSQ_ER_DeliverPoem_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99F_Yash_03",
		"AchievementId": "99F_MSQ_12",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_11",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99F_MSQ_ER_DeliverPoem_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99F_MSQ12_DeliverPoem_title",
		"Description": "@99F_MSQ12_DeliverPoem_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99F_MSQ12_DeliverPoem_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99F_MSQ12_DeliverPoem_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99F_MSQ12_DeliverPoem_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99F_MSQ12_DeliverPoem_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	}
]